



tuantoi1000@gmail.co m Khang Dien Melosa Garden residence, 08,

- 1B Street, Phu Huu Ward, District 9, Thu Duc City, Ho Chi Minh City
- **\** 0933590721
- @tuantoi10000
- /nguyenthanhtuan26.0 2/
- tuantoi1000
- in tuanntt

# Skills



# Nguyễn Thanh Tuấn

## Front-end Developer/Game Designer

My name's Nguyen Thanh Tuan, English name is Finn Nguyen. I am a confident, happy person and have a hobby of traveling alone and exploring the world, so I named my travel series Thanh Tuan Du Ky with the slogan: Life is trips, find your own destination. Besides, I also like to play and research about many game genres such as horror, comedy, action, ..., and my favorite game is League of Legends.

# **Work Experiences**

#### **SUPPORTER**

GOOGLE PRODUCT FORUM VIETNAM

11/2016 - 03/2020

Responsible for working on a range of projects (5 projects at a time), designing appealing websites and interacting on a daily basis with graphic designers, back-end developers, and marketers.

- Support Vietnamese users and advise users on Google products
- such as Chrome, Photos, Drive, Account, Gmail, ...
- Increase the time involved and work to solve high-level product
- problems or customers with product issues.
- Keep up to date with and update knowledge of Google products
- from Google experts.
- Introduce and marketing the Google Product market and
- encourage people to participate in community development and
- promote how to use Google products.

#### COMMUNITY

IVO - Bất Động Sản Sạch

10/2018 - 03/2019

- Develop content and promote IVO articles to the Vietnamese CEO and Real Estate community
- Advertise and develop community groups on IVO and Clean Real Estate managed by IVO and Clean Real Estate.
- Increase the rate of registration and participation of events organized by IVO.
- Updates on the trend of ICO development and thriving on IVO.

# JavaScript ReactJS

lava

Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)

**C**, **C**++, **C**#, **Python** 

MySQL, PL/SQL, NoSQL

**Unreal Engine 5** 

**Adobe Photoshop** 

**Adobe Premiere Pro** 

**Microsoft Office** 

**English** 

**Critical Thinking** 

Community

**Teamwork** 

# **Certificates**

#### **IELTS**

03/2019

IELTS 5.5 with 4 skills: Listening, Speaking, Reading, Writing

**WORD 2010 - EXPERT** 

04/2017

Valid forever and can be taught Word for student.

#### **Community Manager**

JDI ONE - Defily Finance

06/2021 - 02/2022

- Build and develop the community in the Defily project.
- Manage, communicate and interact with members participating in the Defily Finance project.
- Receive tasks given by superiors. Share information from the developers or project managers to members.
- When members have questions related to the Defily project, the Community Manager or Community Members affiliated with the project must answer questions and resolve concerns raised by members.

# Education

## **Computer Science and Technology**

Ton Duc Thang University

09/2017 - 05/2019

- Learn the basics of programming languages such as C, Java.
- Explore and learn about the history and development of Computer Science.
- Finish 2 years of university and transfer to Technical University of Ostrava.

## **Computer Science and Technology**

VSB - Technical University of Ostrava

09/2019 - 08/2023

- Continue studying research-oriented subjects in Computer Science.
- Learn programming languages to build applications such as: C++, C#, Java, Python, HTML5, Database.
- Learn about telecommunications, internet, machine architecture, information systems, machine learning. Build software applications through real-life applications.
- Graduate university with a solo thesis project and complete final state exams.

# **Interests**

- Solo Travel Research Technology Cooking
- ◆ Play game◆ Watch film◆ Photographer

### **Activities**

#### **GOOGLE DEVELOPER GROUP VIETNAM**

#### **COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT LEAD**

12/2017 - 01/2022

- Develop content and promote GDG articles to the IT Vietnam community.
- Advertising and developing IT community groups managed by GDG.
- Increase the rate of registration and participation of GDG events.
- Work directly with businesses, CEOs, IT professionals to create relationships, collaborate and exchange on issues and update developments in IT
- Update on IT and Google development trends.

# Languages

### **English**

Level: Fluent in communication Skills: Good listening, speaking, reading and writing. And use specialized English in the field of Computer Science.

# Prizes and Awards

# TOP 50 VIETNAM - WORD 2010

Microsoft Office Specialist Vietnam

04/2017

IIG Vietnam

# **Projects**

# DEVELOPMENT OF MODERN OF WEB APPLICATIONS - THESIS - SELF PROJECT

#### 09/2021 - 04/2023

Description: The aim of this thesis focuses on nowadays platforms of web applications development. This thesis gives manual, how to select a proper technology framework and how to use it. Besides, with the variety of website development, programmers or designers can self-study, research and develop their own products, students can understand the daily development of web development. web application development platforms and may be updated from time to time.

- Analyze and describe nowadays web frameworks and connected technologies/tools.
- Select one particular way of web app development and describe it in more detail.
- Design case study of some application and describe development process including environment and related tools.
- Implement designed application.
- Evaluate selected framework and environment.

# Scan My QR CODE

